Morning.
Just quickly morning just for two minutes.
Morning, everyone. Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
OK, a couple of things.
Task create other board reflect I think.
And this week's start just I mean I be a
create create.
Prod me.
OK.
Immediately fix.
Yes.
I think you fixed the other, right?
So.
Mm.
So I think because we will have a space
here.
Thank you.
Uh.
Uh, but the production immediately fixed.
OK.
QA agent no.
Uh huh.
Whoa, it's inside.
Help again.
Inside me.
Uh, take.
Anna.
Or or yeah, this we call a task.
Akash immediately check.
Hmm.
Huh. OK. All right, guys. Thank you.
I'll drop.
Yes.
Thank you.
Yeah, thank you.
Thank you.
OK, so let's start quickly.
Or Joby or same code production?
OK.
But up staging staging baby check version.
OK.
TK or Abhi Nikhil in which is a address
here verify. Simply.
Same version code Matlab version same
production or your production pair.
Uh, sorry.
I'm not.
OK, I think it's what is.
But staging me Yogesh,
I think when I give you Kalbi Deka,
staging me thao.
Yeah staging the staging this week.
Nikhil task create miss show me created
Mhm.
task board create like overlapping issue.
Mm.
ORI, all staging environmentally.
Mhm.
Yes.
OK.
Take care. Thank you, Yogesh.
Uh yes,
related bug production preview or staging
preview.
Or Raju Nikhil Nikhil Nikhil.
OK.
Yes.
OK. Thank you, Holly.
Akash.
Uh,
actually we may actually does become like.
Oh, by the way, may I go check around?
Immediately.
OK,
initial login landing page default away,
but other workspace change to dashboard
page shift. W1 say W2 workspace shift.
To the landing page dashboard.
I think it's gonna be.
...
plus icon missing create new quick access
to create group.
Production pay.
Akash.
Plus create new.
I'm missing you.
Garment.
Uh, main instance.
Plus icon group or workspace invite user
plus direct.
I could roll.
Mhm.
And reporting correct workspace change.
Blending blending page.
To you.
Huh.
Ha ha.
OK, good.
Nikhil production I think is all time
apart from that.
Um Yogesh,
your tool based to be a role based pay to
journey role based pay.
Uh, the Vivo Ya create new dikarana.
Take care.
He.
Deployed Ritika or Nikhil?
So take it.
OK.
Oh, Yogesh, can I just same code?
I think it's gonna be.
Oh, send me, send me later.
OK.
Will be up uh.
Shad tester. Take already instance.
Mhm.
Oh.
Mhm.
Ha ha Nick, quickly, dot text.
Well,
my my level I should check the same code
Mhm.
don't know.
No staging maybe for.
Hmm hmm. I think after deployment.
Do you guys anything else?
OK.
Hello. Hi, Madhavi.
Yeah, good morning.
So your laptop's connection sorted.
Yes, yes, yes.
OK. OK. That's fine.
Um, uh,
may I know that are we listed on
Crunchbase?
Sorry.
Our company Scaria dot AI is listed on
Crunchbase.
Do you know anything about that our
listing?
No, I think we need to check.
Orange list.
No,
I think right now don't have anything
about it.
I'm checking. Yeah, we'll get back to.
OK. I'll just ask Mrs.
Nikhil Sir and do the further things
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Uh, please confirm this.
because OK.
OK.
OK, guys.
Thank you everyone.
Thank you.